http://www.bogong.com.au/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
WEBSTORE OPEN | SHOPFRONT CLOSED DUE TO COVID-19 | STILL SHIPPING ORDERS
Bogong EquipmentBogong Equipment
Search:
Search
Ph: 03 9600 0599
gear for serious adventuresAustralia's Leading Store For Outdoor Equipment
Clothing
Men's Outdoor ClothingRainwearSoftshellInsulationShirts & TeesPants & ShortsBase LayerUnderwearWomen's Outdoor ClothingRainwearSoftshellInsulationWomen's Shirts & TopsPants, Shorts & SkirtsBase LayerUnderwearKidsSocksHiking SocksTrail Running SocksSki SocksExpedition SocksGaitersHigh GaitersLow GaitersTrail Running GaitersHeadwearFacemasksSun HatsRain HatsTechnical Warm HeadwearBeaniesCaps, Truckers & VisorsBuffs, Headbands and NeckwarmersGloves & MittsEyewearSunglassesSki GogglesBelay GlassesHigh AltitudeTents
TentsBivy BagsTarpsHammocksTent AccessoriesPacks
Hiking PacksDay PacksTravel PacksDuffles & TotesBaby CarriersHydration PacksWaist & Shoulder BagsSki PacksCamera BagsPack Accessories
Running Packs
Sleep
Sleeping BagsSleeping MatsSleep AccessoriesGear
LightingHeadtorchesLanternsHandheldLighting AccessoriesWalking PolesGear CareRepairProofings & CleanersStraps & BucklesPacking & StorageWaterproof PouchesDry BagsPacking CellsStuff SacksPack LinersStraps & ClipsMountain & Trail RunningTrail ShoesRunning PacksRunning BeltsRunning ApparelHydrationSunglassesSafetyNutritionBikeSkiSkisSki BootsBindingsPolesSkinsWaxing and Ski CareSnowshoes, Boots & SpikesSnow AccessoriesPaddlePaddling accessoriesHydrationBladdersBottlesWater TreatmentAccessoriesFirst Aid KitsKnives & Multi ToolsCook & EatStovesPots & PansUtensils & MugsLightweight Food for Outdoor ActivitiesCamp FurnitureHiking ChairsUltralight TablesNavigationGPS & RescueSuunto WatchesCompassesMap CasesTravelSecurityElectricalBathroomHealthMiscellaneous
Sunglasses
Footwear
Hiking BootsHiking ShoesMountaineering BootsSandalsTrail RunningFootwear Accessories
Climbing Shoes
Snowshoes
Climb
DMM PinkCarabinersLocking carabinersNon-locking carabinersQuickdrawsProtectionCamming DevicesNuts, Hexes, WiresSlings & CordRopesDynamic ropesStatic ropesHarnessesHelmetsRoping DevicesAscendersDescendersBelay DevicesClimbing ShoesClothingAnchors & BoltsMountaineering GearAxes & HammersCramponsIce AnchorsAccessoriesBoulderingAccessoriesChalk BagsChalkNut ToolsHangboards & TrainingRope BagsSlacklinesMiscellaneousAccess
Industrial HarnessRope & WebbingRoping DevicesPulleysCarabiners & MaillonsHelmetsConnectors & LanyardsBags, Rope Protectors, PlatformsBooks
MapsMore BooksHow To BooksNarrativesCoffee Table BooksTravel GuidesPaddleBooksWalk Guides AustralianWalk Guides OverseasCycle GuidesClimbing GuidesMountaineering GuidesSki BooksMagazinesCalendarsSale
SaleWINTER CLEARANCEMen's Winter ClearanceWomen's Winter ClearanceCLIMBING GEARRAINWEAR CLEARANCE
Info
Info
Buying Guides
Newsletters
About Us
Contact Us
Brands
Top Brands
Privacy and Security Details
PrivacyBogong Equipment Pty Ltd (Bogong) is committed to safeguarding personal privacy. Unless given consent to do otherwise, Bogong will only collect and use personal information as set out below.
When a product is purchased personal information may be requested (such as name, address, email, phone numbers) in order to process and deliver your order, and to advise of other related products which may be of interest. We will not reveal your personal information to any external organisation except where necessary for the purpose of fulfilling your order (e.g. financial institutions that issued your credit card and courier companies that deliver your order).
Personal Information will be used for the following purposes:
To enable your order to be processed according to Bogong procedures.
To render services related to Bogong business such as warranty or after sales services.
To provide you with information about products, service and/or special offers.
To obtain opinions or comments about products and/or services.
To record statistical data for marketing analysis.
Bogong recognises the trust with which individuals provide personal information, and such information will not be used or disclosed for any other purposes than those given above without your consent, except in exceptional cases when disclosure may be required by law or is necessary to protect the rights or property of Bogong, or any member of the public.
Email newsletters. If you opt in to receive the Bogong newsletter we will send you an occasional newsletter with information that we hope you will find of interest. You may opt out of this at anytime by using the unsubscribe link in every email.
Bogong may contact individuals using the information which was provided by them in order to:
Enable your order to be processed according to Bogong procedures
Provide information about new products, special offers and other matters relating to your purchase that may be of interest.
To send newsletters about outdoor equipment, tips or information about outdoor equipment, or related matters.
If an individual receives communications from Bogong which they do not wish to receive, they may remove their name from our contact database by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link which is in every communication. This will automatically unsubscribe and this is effective immediately.
Bogong will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any personal information recorded, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. The information is stored on secure servers if in digital format, or in locked areas if in hardcopy format. Bogong employees are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by Bogong. However, security of communications over the Internet cannot be guaranteed, and therefore absolute assurance that information will be secure at all times cannot be given. Bogong will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to personal information.
Bogong provides links to web sites outside of the Bogong site. These linked sites are not under the control of Bogong, and Bogong is not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to the Bogong web site.
Inquiries relating to our Privacy Policy, or any problems or complaints may be directed to the General Manager by calling us at 03 9600 0599.Security
SSL Certificate
The Bogong website has security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information under our control, including credit card information that is submitted to us. When users place orders or access their account information, the Site uses 256-bit secure server software (SSL), which encrypts all information users' input before it is sent to us. In addition, we do not store user's credit card numbers in their online accounts so if someone obtains your account log in information, they will not be able to view a user's credit card number. Thus, we have taken steps to protect the information we collect from you from unauthorised access. Unfortunately, no system is perfect; therefore, Bogong makes no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures. Bogong shall not be responsible for any actual or consequential damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Privacy Policy because of a security breach or technical malfunction.
Google AdWords
The Bogong website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Bogong website. These cookies are not associated with personally identifiable information.
Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you canopt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
About Us
Resources
Contact Bogong Outdoor Equipment Store
Delivery
Bogong Newsletter Archive
Hire
Our Brands
Our Team
© 2020 Bogong Equipment Pty Ltd, Melbourne, Australia. Ph: 03 9600 0599
